<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SymbolSpeak-AAC</string>
    <string name="whatIsAAC">What is AAC?</string>
    <string name="typesOfAAC">Types of AAC</string>
    <string name="peopleWhoNeedAAC">Who is AAC for?</string>
    <string name="defineAAC">Augmentative and alternative communication
        (AAC) is a discipline that studies the ways of communication
        for people with limitations in standard ways of communication such
        as speech.</string>
    <string name="defineTypesOfAac">With technological progress, the assistive
        technologies used in the field of AAK are undergoing major changes.
        Devices are becoming smaller, more sophisticated and easier to use.
        Advances in the field of mobile technologies allow users to choose
        the device they want to use and enable the use of AAK technology for
        people who have not yet been recommended to use it. It is very important
        to adjust the selection of the technique to the cognitive and physical
        capabilities of the person, regardless of the type of technique used.
        Each of the non-tech, low-tech, mid-tech and high-tech techniques are
        adapted to certain groups of users and their different requirements, so
        that each person can find a technique that corresponds to specific
        cognitive and physical abilities. Non-tech techniques are usually used
        with some mid-tech or high-tech technique, and complement each other.
        This technique includes nodding, waving hands, shaking hands, pointing
        with body parts such as a finger, and more. The symbol that will indicate
        a certain body movement is agreed upon between the user and the partner
        who serves as a communication assistant. Low-tech AAK refers to methods
        that are not electronic, but unlike non-tech require some equipment that
        is not part of the body. Low-tech methods are useful because of their
        availability in all moments in which the user can be found in which the
        electronic device is not available, but also because of their availability
        to users who only use AAK temporarily. Mid-tech and high-tech devices
        mainly refer to speech generating devices. Mid-tech devices are electronic
        devices that use batteries and generally have simple functions. High-tech
        devices have more advanced functions than mid-tech devices, such as allowing
        the user to independently define sentences, search the Internet or send
        messages. Such devices have a large number of pages and symbols that the
        user can choose from. High-tech devices can be adapted to various groups
        of users by adjusting the button press time, and the selection can be made
        using the eye or head tracking method, as well as many others.</string>
    <string name="definePeopleWhoNeedAAC">A number of conditions that benefit from
        AAK include Alzheimer\'s disease, Parkinson\'s disease, Down syndrome, autism,
        learning disabilities, developmental disabilities, stroke, cerebral palsy,
        head and brain injuries, amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS), and others.
        In disorders such as dementia and Alzheimer\'s disease, and in head and brain
        injuries, the need for AAK systems appears as a secondary consequence of the
        disorder that causes it. In this group of disorders, there is a wide range
        of difficulties, among which is the inability to determine the meaning of
        words, finding the word that one wants to use, remembering, determining the
        correct answer and following instructions. In this group, help in the form
        of speech therapy occurs more often, and AAK is suggested when speech cannot
        meet daily needs. In a progressive disease such as amyotrophic lateral
        sclerosis, the loss of speech can be gradual or very rapid. Due to the
        impossibility of estimating when speech loss will occur, it is often
        overlooked, and it is important to prioritize the decision regarding
        future plans for communication as the disease progresses. The AAK system
        should be chosen according to the possible limitations that the progress
        of the disease will bring. With the loss of the ability to speak in stroke,
        damage to the vocal cords, and chronic diseases such as Parkinson\'s disease,
        it is assumed that the person knows what they want to say, but cannot say or
        formulate it. In such cases, AAK enables recovery and communication when the
        ability to speak is lost, so that the person is not isolated or feels lonely.
        Developmental disabilities, learning disabilities, Down syndrome and autism
        are disorders that appear at birth and develop throughout childhood. When
        learning how to use the AAK system, users with the mentioned difficulties
        require a communication partner who shows by their own example how to use
        the system, and through the use of the system they require help in the
        decision process in order to successfully express their decision through
        the use of the system.</string>
</resources>